[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What house is Harry Potter in?",
      "options": ["Gryffindor", "Slytherin", "Ravenclaw", "Hufflepuff"],
      "correctAnswer": "Gryffindor"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What is Hermione’s last name?",
      "options": ["Weasley", "Granger", "Lovegood", "Black"],
      "correctAnswer": "Granger"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What magical sport does Harry play?",
      "options": ["Gobstones", "Quidditch", "Wizard Chess", "Exploding Snap"],
      "correctAnswer": "Quidditch"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What is the spell to turn lights on?",
      "options": ["Lumos", "Nox", "Alohomora", "Accio"],
      "correctAnswer": "Lumos"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Who is the potions master at Hogwarts?",
      "options": ["Snape", "McGonagall", "Hagrid", "Dumbledore"],
      "correctAnswer": "Snape"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "What is Ron's pet rat’s name?",
      "options": ["Fang", "Scabbers", "Crookshanks", "Norbert"],
      "correctAnswer": "Scabbers"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What animal can Professor McGonagall turn into?",
      "options": ["Cat", "Dog", "Snake", "Owl"],
      "correctAnswer": "Cat"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "What platform is used to board the Hogwarts Express?",
      "options": ["9", "10", "9 3/4", "8 1/2"],
      "correctAnswer": "9 3/4"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Who is Harry’s godfather?",
      "options": ["Sirius Black", "Severus Snape", "Arthur Weasley", "Remus Lupin"],
      "correctAnswer": "Sirius Black"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Who is the headmaster of Hogwarts?",
      "options": ["Dumbledore", "Snape", "Voldemort", "Grindelwald"],
      "correctAnswer": "Dumbledore"
    }
  ]
  